<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Ranco Response</title>
    <link>https://ranco-disaster.netlify.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Ranco Response</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 05:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ranco-disaster.netlify.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About Us</title>
      <link>https://ranco-disaster.netlify.com/about-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ranco-disaster.netlify.com/about-us/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amenities</title>
      <link>https://ranco-disaster.netlify.com/amenities/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ranco-disaster.netlify.com/amenities/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Business Continuity</title>
      <link>https://ranco-disaster.netlify.com/business-continuity/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ranco-disaster.netlify.com/business-continuity/</guid>
      <description>Ranco Response has extensive experience providing code compliant facilities to satisfy disruptions to ongoing operations. These OSHA compliant facilities support disaster response, temporary functional space during renovations or work continuation services, and turnaround/shutdown support.Our solutions are rapidly deployable, nationally based, modular, and scalable so they can fit where needed and support your specific needs. The equipment can support all facets of business including retail, pharmacy, grocery, office, convenience store, staff accommodations, and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact Us</title>
      <link>https://ranco-disaster.netlify.com/contact-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ranco-disaster.netlify.com/contact-us/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Emergency Response</title>
      <link>https://ranco-disaster.netlify.com/emergency-response/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ranco-disaster.netlify.com/emergency-response/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Emergency Response</title>
      <link>https://ranco-disaster.netlify.com/emergency-response/more-info/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ranco-disaster.netlify.com/emergency-response/more-info/</guid>
      <description>In an emergency response scenario, time is of the essence with the safety of responders and the impacted population hinging on mission critical resources. Ranco Response, through code-compliant equipment ownership, proven processes modeled after National Incident Management System and Incident Command System, and accountability at all levels of the organization, stands ready to meet the demands of first responders.
Engineered Soft Wall Structures – Climate controlled tent facilities with floors, lights, doors, safety packages, and fire extinguishers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Event Support</title>
      <link>https://ranco-disaster.netlify.com/event-support/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ranco-disaster.netlify.com/event-support/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Event Support</title>
      <link>https://ranco-disaster.netlify.com/event-support/more-info/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ranco-disaster.netlify.com/event-support/more-info/</guid>
      <description>When little to no infrastructure is available to meet the demands of festival attendees or other special events, Ranco Response provides the temporary facilities to ensure the health and comfort of the visiting population. All facilities and systems are assimilated into existing infrastructure and operated in accordance with all federal, state, and local guidelines with the safety of the attendees the number one priority.
Ranco Response has a long-standing history of providing innovative solutions to the special events industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Facilities Support</title>
      <link>https://ranco-disaster.netlify.com/facilities-support/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ranco-disaster.netlify.com/facilities-support/</guid>
      <description>Ranco Response provides janitorial, maintenance, trash disposal, security guards and services, mail routing, reception, laundry, and other related services to support operations to both government-owned and contractor-owned facilities. With a focus on safety, efficiency, sustainability, and quality, Ranco Response maintains the infrastructure in proper operating conditions through routine, preventative maintenance and safety checks, helping to prevent operational failure, reducing operating costs and allowing occupants to focus on their core mission.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Logistics Support</title>
      <link>https://ranco-disaster.netlify.com/logistics-support/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ranco-disaster.netlify.com/logistics-support/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Logistics Support</title>
      <link>https://ranco-disaster.netlify.com/logistics-support/more-info/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ranco-disaster.netlify.com/logistics-support/more-info/</guid>
      <description>Ranco Response augments the existing capabilities of both military and commercial entities. We deliver, setup, operate and maintain all of the equipment, allowing our customers to focus on their mission, whether it is a military training event or a business continuity situation or any enduring facility support mission, Ranco Response is there.
Workspaces, conference rooms, storage areas, temporary power, communications, warehousing, Material Handling Equipment, and turnkey on-site support
Staff accommodation and work continuation facilities include housing, food service, communications (voice/data), laundry equipment &amp;amp; services, showers, restrooms, and all temporary utilities as required.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LSA Support</title>
      <link>https://ranco-disaster.netlify.com/lsa-support/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ranco-disaster.netlify.com/lsa-support/</guid>
      <description>When little to no infrastructure is available to meet the demands of festival attendees or other special events, Ranco Response provides the temporary facilities to ensure the health and comfort of the visiting population. All facilities and systems are assimilated into existing infrastructure and operated in accordance with all federal, state, and local guidelines with the safety of the attendees the number one priority.
Ranco Response has a long-standing history of providing innovative solutions to the special events industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Structures</title>
      <link>https://ranco-disaster.netlify.com/structures/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ranco-disaster.netlify.com/structures/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tactical Operations Centers</title>
      <link>https://ranco-disaster.netlify.com/tactical-operations-centers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ranco-disaster.netlify.com/tactical-operations-centers/</guid>
      <description>Tactical Operation Centers can be provided in the form of climate-controlled clear-span structures complete with sidewalls, doors, wood flooring, lighting, exit signs, fire extinguishers, and HVAC. Tents are sized based on client requirements and range from 500 square feet to 30,000 square feet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thank You</title>
      <link>https://ranco-disaster.netlify.com/thank-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ranco-disaster.netlify.com/thank-you/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Turnkey Camps</title>
      <link>https://ranco-disaster.netlify.com/turnkey-camps/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ranco-disaster.netlify.com/turnkey-camps/</guid>
      <description>Whenever groups of people need to be relocated or are temporarily displaced, there is a need for provisional life support facilities to sustain them. These relocations or displacements can be due to natural disasters, civil disruptions, migrant populations, mass gatherings, or military maneuvers.
The following is a list of items that typically comprise a turnkey Base Camp operation. All, portions or single items from this list can be provided for short or long durations.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>