<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Ranco Response</title>
    <link>https://ranco-disaster.netlify.com/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Ranco Response</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 05:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ranco-disaster.netlify.com/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Emergency Response</title>
      <link>https://ranco-disaster.netlify.com/emergency-response/more-info/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ranco-disaster.netlify.com/emergency-response/more-info/</guid>
      <description>In an emergency response scenario, time is of the essence with the safety of responders and the impacted population hinging on mission critical resources. Ranco Response, through code-compliant equipment ownership, proven processes modeled after National Incident Management System and Incident Command System, and accountability at all levels of the organization, stands ready to meet the demands of first responders.
Engineered Soft Wall Structures – Climate controlled tent facilities with floors, lights, doors, safety packages, and fire extinguishers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Event Support</title>
      <link>https://ranco-disaster.netlify.com/event-support/more-info/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ranco-disaster.netlify.com/event-support/more-info/</guid>
      <description>When little to no infrastructure is available to meet the demands of festival attendees or other special events, Ranco Response provides the temporary facilities to ensure the health and comfort of the visiting population. All facilities and systems are assimilated into existing infrastructure and operated in accordance with all federal, state, and local guidelines with the safety of the attendees the number one priority.
Ranco Response has a long-standing history of providing innovative solutions to the special events industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Logistics Support</title>
      <link>https://ranco-disaster.netlify.com/logistics-support/more-info/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ranco-disaster.netlify.com/logistics-support/more-info/</guid>
      <description>Ranco Response augments the existing capabilities of both military and commercial entities. We deliver, setup, operate and maintain all of the equipment, allowing our customers to focus on their mission, whether it is a military training event or a business continuity situation or any enduring facility support mission, Ranco Response is there.
Workspaces, conference rooms, storage areas, temporary power, communications, warehousing, Material Handling Equipment, and turnkey on-site support
Staff accommodation and work continuation facilities include housing, food service, communications (voice/data), laundry equipment &amp;amp; services, showers, restrooms, and all temporary utilities as required.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>